Guide to the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, Local 3 Records and Photographs WAG.135
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Shop Files, 1964-1989
  - Shops Closed, E.W.H. Bakeries, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Shops Closed, Fama Bake Shop, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Shops Closed, Family Bakers Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Shops Closed, Famous Bakery, 1966-1979 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Shops Closed, Far Rockaway Bake Shop, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Shops Closed, Fay Bron Bake Shop Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Shops Closed, Baisly Pastries Inc., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Shops Closed, Foster Avenue Bakery Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Shops Closed, Foursome Steak Pub, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Shops Closed, Fren Kosher (Formerly Saro Bakery), 1966-1968 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Shops Closed, Friedman's Bakery, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Shops Closed, G&C Bakery Inc., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Shops Closed, G&G Bake Shop Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Shops Closed, G&K Bakery, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Shops Closed, Gach Pastry Shop (Formerly: Parfait Pastrie), 1967-1971 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Shops Closed, Getty Square, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Shops Closed, Gilmore Cafeteria (DBA Ratners), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Shops Closed, Glen Cove Bake Shop, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Shops Closed, Glendale Bake Shop, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Shops Closed, Goldfinger Bake Shop Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Shops Closed, H&M Bake Shop Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Shops Closed, Hanew Bake Shop, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Shops Closed, Happy Bakers Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Shops Closed, Heisler's Pastry Shop, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Shops Closed, Henry's Retail Shop Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Shops Closed, Home Bakery (Formerly: Joseph Arzt Bake Shop), 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Shops Closed, Hungry Harbor Road Bake Shop (Formerly: Teena's Cake Box), 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Shops Closed, Hunt's Bakery (Formerly: Clark's), 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Shops Closed, IRG Bake Shop, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Shops Closed, Imperial Bake Shop, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Shops Closed, J.A.R. Bake Shop Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Shops Closed, Janz Bake Shop Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Shops Closed, Jay Bird, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Shops Closed, Jo-Cin, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Shops Closed, Jo Frank Baking Corp., 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Shops Closed, Joblan Homestyle Bakery Inc., 1965 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Shops Closed, Kaiserman Bakery, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Shops Closed, Karen's Garden Bakery Corp., 1964- 1966 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Shops Closed, Kastner Bakery (Formerly: Budapest Pastry), 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Shops Closed, Kent Bakery Co., 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Shops Closed, L&M Bake Shop, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Shops Closed, L.S.M. Bake Shop (Formerly: Eden Rock Bakery), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Shops Closed, La Pattisserie Inc., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Shops Closed, Lederer's Bakery, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Shops Closed, Leha Bake Shop Inc., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Shops Closed, Lucullus Cake Shop Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Shops Closed, Lushell Bakery Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Shops Closed, M&M Bake Shop, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Shops Closed, Mahler's Pastry Shop, 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Shops Closed, Man-Mack Bake Shop, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Shops Closed, Mars Cookie Co. Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Shops Closed, Mary Julie Baking Co., 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Shops Closed, Mayer Bake Shop Inc., 1967 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Shops Closed, Metro-Hardoon Bakery, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Shops Closed, Meyerson-Gerlan Bake Shop Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Shops Closed, Mosel Bake Shop Inc. (DBA Peter Pan), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Shops Closed, Moses Ginsberg Bakery, 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Shops Closed, Nasch's Pastry Shop, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Shops Closed, Nassau Bake Shop, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Shops Closed, Net Joy Bialey's Inc., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Shops Closed, Netello Bakery (Formerly: Marlene Bake Shop), 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Shops Closed, Nevada (R.&L. Bakers Inc.), 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Shops Closed, New Normandie Cropsey Bake Shop, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Shops Closed, None Better Bakery Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Shops Closed, Normandie, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Shops Closed, Normandy, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Shops Closed, 115 Bake Shop, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Shops Closed, Oneg Bakery, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Shops Closed, Our Own Place Bakery Co., 1965 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Shops Closed, Oven Fresh Bakery, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Shops Closed, Oyster Bay Pastries Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Shops Closed, Paradise, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Shops Closed, Paris Bakery, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Shops Closed, Passer (Formerly: Enbee Bake Shop), 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Shops Closed, Pastry Fair (a.k.a. Irene's Bake Shop), 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Shops Closed, Paul Mar Bakery, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Shops Closed, Philip's Pastry Shop, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Shops Closed, Pickwick Bake Shop, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Shops Closed, Pomerantz Bake Shop, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Shops Closed, Poznanski's Bakery (a.k.a. Aries Food Shop), 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Shops Closed, Quality Bakery, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Shops Closed, R&W Bake Shop Inc., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Shops Closed, Reliable Bakery, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Shops Closed, Richman's Bakery (a.k.a. A&S Bake Shop Inc.), 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Shops Closed, Richmond Hill Bakery, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Shops Closed, Ritz Bakery, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Shops Closed, Rojo Bakery, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Shops Closed, Ron-Mar Pastries Inc. (a.k.a. Luxor Bake Shop), 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Shops Closed, Ros-Mar Bake Shop Inc., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Shops Closed, Rosenberg Bakery, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Shops Closed, Rovelle Bakers Inc., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Shops Closed, Royal Bake Shop (Formerly: S.D.R. Bake Shop), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Shops Closed, Rutta's Bake Shop, 1969-1976 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Shops Closed, S&J Bake Shop Inc., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Shops Closed, S.M.J. Bakeries Ltd., 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Shops Closed, Sally Bake Shop Inc. (Formerly: Archer Bake Shop), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Shops Closed, Sally's Home Baking, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Shops Closed, Sapirstein Bakery, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Shops Closed, Schaffers Bakery, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Shops Closed, Schulers, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Shops Closed, Sheldon Bake Shop, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Shops Closed, Sheridan Bake Shop, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Shops Closed, Shomer Shabos Baking Corp., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Shops Closed, Shomer Shabes Bake Shop Inc., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Shops Closed, Shlucker's Bakery, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Shops Closed, Shlucker's Bakery Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Shops Closed, Sigmas Bake Shop (a.k.a. Greggs; Craig Bakery), 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Shops Closed, Station Bakery, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Shops Closed, Stroells Bake Shop, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Shops Closed, Stuhmer Baking Corp., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Shops Closed, Sutter Bake Shop Inc., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Shops Closed, Three Emm's Bake Shop Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Shops Closed, Topps Baking Corp., 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Shops Closed, Town Fair Bake Shop, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Shops Closed, Tov Bake Shop Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Shops Closed, Town Rose Bakery, 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Shops Closed, Vernon Bakery Corp., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Shops Closed, Versailles Bakery Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Shops Closed, Victoria Bake Shop Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Shops Closed, Weiss and Franczoz Inc., 1966 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Shops Closed, Westwood Bake Shop, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Shops Closed, Winky's Bake Shop (Formerly: Max Zip Pastry Inc.), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Shops Closed, Zee's Bakery, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Shops Closed, Zaro Bake Shop, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Shops Closed, Zion, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 78)
- Series V: Local 3, Subjects, 1954-1989
  This series contains election fliers, ballot and campaign materials from the 1950s through the 1980s that offer insight into the evolution of the union. A union label file provides excellent and colorful examples of union labels for bread. Also of interest are the files that document corruption within the baking trade in the early 1960s (See: James Cross; Daniel Motto). Many of these subject files may have been used as research material in the monthly publication of "The Local 3 News." Michael Sandroff's notes for the Local 3's 1967 publication of its history, "Progress Through Unity," can also be found here as can his unpublished memoir "I Paid My Dues."
  - General Files/Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - General Files/Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - General Files/Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - General Files/Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - General Files/Correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - By-Laws, 1958, 1964, 1969, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - By-Laws Committee, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - History: M. Sandroff (Unpublished Manuscript: "I Paid My Dues"), undated (Box 21, Folder 8a)
  - History of the Formation of the Bakers Union in New York (Solarchik, J.), 1983 (Box 21, Folder 8b)
  - Administrative Slate Committee, Minutes and Proceedings, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Slate Committee, Material for the Leaflet, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration and Holidays, 1962, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Awards, 25/40 Year Membership, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - BCT, Pennsylvania State Board, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - BCT, Regional Council-1st & 2nd, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Bakers Union 75th Anniversary Material, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Biscuit Contracts, Survey Conducted by BCT, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Biscuit Council Convention Atlanta, GA, Jun 11, 1983-Jun 16, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16a)
  - Black History Month Program, Feb 22, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - (George) Block Material (Background for 75th Anniversary), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Cake & Trade Exhibit, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Cake & Trade Exhibit, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Cake & Trade Exhibit, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Christmas Cookie List, 1978-1982 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Cohn, Glickstein, Lurie, Ostrin, Lubell & Lubell, Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1983 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Contract Review Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Contract Review Committee, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Conventions & Conferences (Misc.), 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Cross-E. Moschetta, et al v. James Cross, et al/H. Alvino v. BCW, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Cross Indictment & Background, 1956-1963 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - DeConcini, John, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Dinners & Special Events, Ticket Ledger, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - (Frank) Dutto Banquet, Jun 4, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Eastern Central Conference, 1978-1982 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Eastern Central Conference, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Elections, Ballots, Leaflets, Campaign Material, 1958-1965 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Elections, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Elections, 1979-1989 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Executive Board, 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - First Regional Council, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Forms, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Grievance Board, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Health & Safety Material, 1970-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Horn & Hardart (Philadelphia), 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Kralstein Address to Local 3, Dec 15, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Leaves of Absence, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Legal, V. Fertig, et al v. Kralstein (BCWIUA), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Legal, Kipbea Baking Co./H&L Baking Co. v Local 3, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Motto, Daniel/Local 350, Marcus Indictment, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Officer's Retirement, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Organization Reports, Jan 1968 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Pension Fund, International, 1975-1983 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Picnic Committee, Minutes, Fliers, Misc., 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Outline and Notes, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research for Introduction, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research for Contracts, 1955-1958 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research for Contracts (Tables) Locals 1, 3, 17, 164, 579, 1955-1964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research Pie Shop Contracts, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research Organizing, 1955-1960 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research Health and Welfare, 1955-1962 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research Activities (clippings), 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research, Membership, Merger and Finances, 1954-1962 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research Labor Department, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research Reunification, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Progress Through Unity: The Local 3 Story Research Union Function, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Poor People's Campaign, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Resolutions Submitted by Local 3 at 28th Convention, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Rondou, Rene-Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Safety, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Scholarships, Correspondence, Applications, 1977, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Senior Citizens, Local 3 Seniors Club and General Clippings, undated, circa 1970-1989 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Shop Steward Material, Guides and Manuals, [1950-1969] (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Shop Steward Material, Info. Packet (TWUA), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Shop StewardMaterial, Class Related Material, 1957, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Strike Ballot, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Structure Committee, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Summons, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Trustee Reports, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Union Label, Shop Stamps, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Series VI: Welfare and Pension Fund, 1955-1988
  This series contains the records of two separate entities, the Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund of Local 51 and the Local 3 Welfare and Pension Fund. With the merger of these two unions in 1973 Harry Lorber became the Chairman of the Board of Trustees for both organizations. The inequity between the two funds was the source of pre-merger negotiation and documents related to this can be found in the general files and correspondence of the early 1970s. Further information about this issue can be found in the papers of Local 51 which are located in Series VII.
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Plan Description and Summary, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Correspondence and Bills, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, General Files, Agreements, Financial, Legal, Minutes, 1954-1972 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Affidavits, Pensioners A-E, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Affidavits, Pensioners F-J, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Affidavits, Pensioners K-R, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Affidavits, Pensioners S, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Affidavits, Pensioners T-Z, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Financial Statements/Funds, 1953-1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Financial Statements/Reports, 1964-1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Financial Statements/Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Financial Statements/Reports, 1978-1984 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Mortgage Title Company, 1957-1988 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Mortgage, Lawrence #1 Corporation, 1968-1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Cake Bakers Union Welfare Fund, Pension Committee/Henry Lorber, [1960-1969] (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Local 3, Welfare and Pension Fund, General Files/Correspondence, undated, 1974-1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Local 3, Welfare and Pension Fund, General Files/Correspondence, 1983, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Local 3, Welfare and Pension Fund, Pension Fund Report, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Local 3, Welfare and Pension Fund, Pension Fund Report, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Local 3, Welfare and Pension Fund, Retirement Benefit Plan, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Series VII: General Files, 1902-1978
  Included in this series are the general files and correspondence of the original six unions (Locals 1, 3, 17, 164, 579) that merged to create Local 3 in 1955 as well as a number of other local unions that subsequently merged with Local 3 including Cake Baker's Union Local 51. Insurance claim forms in English and in German from old Local 3, dating from the turn of the century, are located here and represent the oldest documents in the Collection. Also of note are election leaflets from Local 338 which are in Yiddish. Of particular interest are the merger-related documents, including a file on the proposed alliance between the Bakers Union and the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Included are papers that cover the meetings and negotiations that preceded the 1955 merger, the reunification of the International Union, and the merger between Locals 3 and 51. NOTE: Boxes 25 is missing as of March 2011.
  - Amalgamated Food Workers, 5th Biennial Convention, Dec 7, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - American Bakery & Confectionery Workers Union (ABC), 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bagel Bakers Council of Greater New York v. Local 338, Court Documents, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Bagel Bakers Council of Greater New York v. Local 338, Court Documents, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Bagel Bakers Council of Greater New York v. Local 338, Court Documents, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Bagel Bakers Council of Greater New York, J. Silverman v. NLRB, US Court of Appeals, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Bagel Bakers Council of Greater New York et al v. NLRB, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Bagel Bakers Council of Greater New York, Correspondence Related to Backpay Claims, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Baking Industry Labor-Management Apprentice Council of Greater New York, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Baking Industry Labor-Management Apprentice Council of Greater New York, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Charter for Local 51 and Certificates, 1953-1969 (Box Shared Tamiment XOS002)
  - Journeymen Bakers Union, Local 1 -- Incorporation Documents, 1917-1954 (Box Shared Tamiment 193, Folder 11)
  - Jurisdiction, Hearing Transcript, Oct 20, 1952 - Oct 22, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Jurisdiction, Wilson-Jacobi, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Local 1, General Files/Correspondence/Financial Reports, 1917-1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Local 1, Elections, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Local 1, 62nd Anniversary Cake Show Record, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Old Local 3, General Files/Correspondence, [1930-1949] (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application A-B, 1903-1933 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application C-D, 1915-1927 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application E-G, 1911-1934 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application H, 1906-1933 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application J, 1919-1933 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application K-L, 1902-1934 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application M, 1902-1933 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application N-O, 1916-1932 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application P-R, 1904-1931 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application S, 1916-1934 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application T-V, 1913-1933 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Old Local 3, International Sick & Death Benefit Fund Application W-Z, 1918-1931 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Local 6, Dues Ledger, 1948; 2013.026 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    Scope and Content Note
    Dues ledger of Eugene Rupp.
  - Local 17, General Files/Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Local 17, General Files/Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Local 50, "Bakers' Voice" Newsletter, Leaflets, Clippings, Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Local 50, Legal, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Local 51, By-Laws, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Local 51, Dues Books (Joseph Bless), 1912-1923, 1948-1951 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Local 51, General Files/Correspondence/Financial Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Local 51, General Files/Correspondence/Election Materials, 1953-1955 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Local 51, General Files/Correspondence, 1959-1961, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Local 51, Banquet Programs, Correspondence, 1940-1962 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Local 51, Erlich 50th Wedding Anniversary, Cake and Art Exhibit, Feb 28, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Local 164, General Files, Correspondence, Fliers, Misc. Members List, 1945-1955 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Local 338 General Files, 1944-1966 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Local 338, Elections, 1948-1966 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Local 338, Correspondence, Feb 1963 - Dec 1964 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Local 338, Correspondence, Jan 1965 - May 1971 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Local 579, William F. Schnitzer Testimonial Dinner, Guest Lists, Speeches, Telegrams, Dec 20, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Mergers, Locals 1, 3, 17, 164, 164B, 22, 50, 51, 258, 288, 350, 491, 579, 1941-1947 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Mergers, Merger Related Publications, 1946-1955 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Mergers, B&C Teamsters Affiliations, 1958-1968 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mergers, ABC and B&C First Merger Convention, Dec 4, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Mergers, Local 3 and Local 51, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Mergers, Local 3 and Local 51, Uniform Language Contract, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Series VIII: Souvenir Programs, 1930-1993